(サイ)天地橋周辺に人の気配はない。
I don't sense the presence of
anyone around the Tenchi Bridge...
I guess that means there won't
be any Akatsuki ambush, huh...?
(ヤマト)暁の待ち伏せ
という線は消えたか。
All right! Then let's proceed
as planned.
よし それでは
予定どおり行動しよう。
Right!
(ナルト)おう！
Naruto.
ナルト すまないが これを持って➡
Could you take this and
hold it towards me?
ボクのほうへ向けてくれないか？
(ヤマト)よし いいぞ
こっちに向けてくれ。
All right, that's good.
Hold it towards me.
Wood Style: Transformation!
木遁変化！
どうだ？ うまくいったか？
So? Did it turn out okay?
(サクラ)はい！ どこから見ても
サソリの傀儡 ヒルコそのものです。
Yes, it did!
You look like Sasori's puppet
Hiruko in every way.
では 声の調子を
合わせておきたい。
Now I want to adjust the voice.
Let me know when it sounds right.
いいところで ストップをかけてくれ。
Yes, sir!
はい。
あっあっ あぁ～…。
ああぁ～…。
Oh!
That's it. That's the voice.
あっ それそれ！ そんな声です。
それじゃあ これより
作戦に入るからね。
Then we're going to start
the operation, okay?
Your tone is too polite.
口調が丁寧すぎます。
You need to sound more violent
or surly or something...
もっと こう 乱暴っていうか➡
ぶっきらぼうっていうか…。
Oh... That's right.
あぁ そうだったね。
I'm irritable, and hate waiting
and being kept waiting.
人を待つのも待たせるのも
嫌いな➡
短気な性格だ。
Okay, we're starting the operation!
では 今から作戦に入るぞ！
ウハハハッ！ そうそう
そんな感じだったってばよ。
Right-right.
That's what he was like!
Okay, our opponent should be
on the alert. We'll split up now!
(ヤマト)では
相手も警戒しているはず。
ここからは別行動だ。
Observe teamwork at all times!
Especially you, Naruto!
だが チームワーク厳守だ。
特にナルト
合図前に飛び出すんじゃねえぞ。
Don't be jumping out before
I give the signal!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
《ヤマト : さて 行くか》
Okay... Time to go.
《サクラ : 風が強い… これなら！》
The wind's strong. This should...
Sakura-chan...
《サクラちゃん…》
Yeah, this spot should be okay.
《サクラ : うん… ここならいい》
《サクラ : そろそろ正午…》
It's almost noon...
まだかよ!? スパイ野郎は…。
That spy jerk... isn't he here yet?
(サイ)アイツか…。
Is that him?
You are my friend.
you are my friend
Ah that day's dream...
aa ano hi no yume
You haven't forgotten it, have you?
ima demo mada wasuretenain deshou
You are my dream.
you are my dream
Ah it had just started your one longest way.
aa hajimatta bakka kimi no one longest way
Woah, I'm starting on a journey now!
woah ima tabidatsu yo
EVERDAY hereafter is a shining day.
everyday kono saki mo shining day
Unchanging singin', a bright morning smile.
kawarazu singin' hikaru asa no smile
This is the last farewell on funny days.
kore de miosame no funny days
Leaping into the future I see. Go far, dream of my heart.
tobidatsu future mezashita go far kokoro no dream of
I'll go the distance, the endless sky is blue.
i'll go the distance mihatenu sora wa blue
I've hitched a ride on the star ship, this is the best forever trip.
norikonda star ship kore ga saigo no forever trip
You are my friend.
you are my friend
Ah that day's dream...
aa ano hi no yume
You haven't forotten it, have you?
ima demo mada wasuretenai deshou
You are my dream.
you are my dream
Ah, it had just started your one longest way.
aa hajimatta bakka kimi no one longest way
Woah, I'm starting on a journey now!
woah ima tabidatsu yo
Thank you my friend.
thank you my friend
Ah even now,
aa ano hi no koto
I still remember that day.
ima demo mada oboeteru kara
You are my dream.
you are my dream
Ah those days that will never come back.
aa mou nidoto sou modoranai days
Woah I'll go the distance!
woah i'll go the distance
The Tenchi Bridge
来たってばよ。
Here he comes.
((サソリ : 草隠れの里にある
天地橋に➡
At midday in ten days,
go to the Tenchi Bridge
located in
the Village Hidden in the Grass!
十日後の真昼に行け。
大蛇丸の部下に オレのスパイがいる。
I've got a spy working as one
of Orochimaru's subordinates...
(そこで ソイツと落ち合う…
ことになって…))
I was supposed to
rendezvous... with him... there...
《ヤマト : アイツか…》
That's him, huh...?
《サクラ : ヤマト隊長…
うまくやってよ》
Captain Yamato...
I hope you do okay...
お久しぶりです… サソリ様。
It's been a long time, Sasori-sama.
《コイツは…》
He's...
(カブト)５年ぶりですね。
It's been five years, hasn't it?
Yakushi Kabuto...
《薬師 カブト…》
尾行は？
Were you followed...?
大丈夫です。
We're okay...
(ヤマト)調子はどうだ？
How're you doing?
(カブト)サソリ様の術が解け➡
I've still got the strange sensation...
自分が何者であるか
思い出したときの➡
from when I remembered who I was
after your Jutsu broke...
奇妙な気分が残ってて…。
まだ少し 頭が重いです。
I still feel heavy-headed...
Him again...?!
また アイツか！
Who would've thought...
the Akatsuki spy was Kabuto.
まさか 暁のスパイが
カブトだったなんて…。
(ヤマト)いくつか質問する。
I've got some questions for you.
(カブト)時間がありませんから
手短にお願いします。
I don't have much time,
so please keep it short.
大蛇丸の目を盗んで
ここまで来るのも➡
I risked my life to get here
without Orochimaru finding out.
命がけですから。
アジトの場所と➡
I want information about
うちは サスケについての情報をくれ。
the location of his hideout
and Uchiha Sasuke.
アジトは いくつもあって➡
There are several hideouts.
居場所がバレぬよう 一週単位で➡
We move to
a different hideout each week
so as not to get discovered.
各所を転々と移動しています。
Of course there are hideouts,
(カブト)それは もちろん
音隠れの里以外の➡
not just in the Village Hidden
in the Sound, but in other lands as well.
他国にもあって 大蛇丸のスパイが
入り込んで 手引きしています。
Spies for Orochimaru infiltrate
and act as informers.
But there are all sorts of
means of transport,
ただ 移動手段もまちまちで
そう簡単には…。
so they're not easily tracked...
(ヤマト)今は？
Where is it now?
We're now in a hideout
今は 北の湖の小島の
アジトに潜伏していて➡
on a small island on
a lake to the north.
あと 三日で移動します。
We'll be moving again in three days.
(カブト)そこに うちは サスケもいます。
Uchiha Sasuke is there as well.
The sound of the wind is so loud
I can't hear anything.
風の音が強くって
全然 聞き取れねえってばよ。
You idiot! That's why we were
able to get this close.
(サクラ)バカね！ だからこそ
逆に 私たちも➡
ここまで近寄れるんじゃない。
The wind blows away the noise and
smell, so we can sit here unnoticed.
音も匂いも
風が飛ばしてくれるから➡
気づかれないのよ！
By the way...
ところで…。
Oh... it's just a wild rabbit.
なんだ… 野ウサギか…。
ところで… サソリ様より
命ぜられていた➡
By the way...
About what you ordered me to do,
Sasori-sama...
例の件ですが…。
《やばいな… 今のうちに
聞き出しておきたいことが➡
Uh oh...
I still had a few more things
I wanted to ask him
while I had the chance, but...
もう少しあったが…➡
これ以上会話を続けると
ボロが出る…》
I'll be discovered if the conversation
continues any further...
(カブト)大蛇丸は転生後も➡
Even after his reincarnation,
使い捨てた遺体の細胞標本に
術でプロテクトをかけていて➡
Orochimaru uses a Jutsu
to apply a protector
to the cellular specimens
from his discarded body...
その細胞データを 解析することは
ボクには できませんでした。
And therefore I was unable
to analyze the cellular data.
そうか…。
I see...
What's he doing?!
He should just grab him!
な～にしてんだってばよ！
さっさと 捕らえりゃ
いいじゃねえか！
相手は あのカブトよ！
His opponent is Kabuto.
慎重すぎるくらいで
ちょうどいいのよ。
Being overly cautious is just fine.
It's all over if he gets away, right?
もし 取り逃がしでもしたら
おしまいでしょ？
(サイ)でも…➡
But...
あまり慎重になりすぎて
怪しまれたら➡
The spy could get suspicious
if he's too cautious...
拘束するタイミングを失うよ。
and the timing to capture him
will get thrown off.
それは… ヤマト隊長を
信じるしかないわ。
We'll...
just have to believe in
Captain Yamato about that...
(カブト)では すぐにでも
例のものを渡してください。
Now, please hand over
the item in question immediately.
ボクも これ以上
ゆっくりしていられません。
I can't be hanging around here
any longer.
(カブト)ここで あなたと
こうしていることが バレたら➡
If it's discovered that I'm here
with you like this...
ボクは 殺されてしまう…。
I'll be killed.
Okay...
わかった…。
《限界だな… もう ここらへんで
やるしかない！》
I can't hold out any longer...
I just have to capture him
here and now!
That conversation sounds interesting.
(大蛇丸)おもしろそうな話ね。
Would you guys let me
join in as well?
(大蛇丸)私も会話に
混ぜてもらえるかしら？
《あっ！ つけられてたか！》
He was followed!
大蛇丸！
あ…。
Orochimaru!
《あれが…》
That's...?
If you hadn't pulled out
a Kunai Knife,
サソリ様がクナイを出さなければ➡
I wouldn't have been able
to get away before I noticed.
気づかずに
逃げ遅れるところでした。
《うまい具合に勘違い
してくれたようだな…➡
It looks like he's
misunderstood nicely...
I guess I still haven't been
discovered for now...
とりあえずは バレずに済んだか…。
しかし 大蛇丸が
出てきたとなると…➡
But... now that Orochimaru
has shown up...
さて… どうする？》
What should I do?
その装束 懐かしいわね サソリ…。
That outfit... sure takes me back...
Sasori...
カブトをつけてきたのか？
Did you follow Kabuto?
なに 少し礼を
言おうと思ってね…。
Oh... I just thought I'd thank you.
あなたが送り込んでくれたこの子
すごく重宝したわ…。
This kid you sent to me...
has come in very handy.
The number of human subjects
necessary for the development
(大蛇丸)新しい術を
一つ開発するのに必要な➡
of one new Jutsu is over a hundred...
人体実験の数は100体以上…。
(大蛇丸)使い終わった実験体も
この子の医療忍術のおかげで➡
Thanks to this kid's Medical Ninjutsu,
I've been able to reuse
test subjects several times.
何度も
使いまわすことが出来たわ…。
There's been a great shortage
of them, you see...
実験体も
なかなか不足しててね…。
どうすんだってばよ!?
What do we do?!
(サクラ)隊長の指示があるまでは
待機するしかないわ。
We just have to stand by until
the Captain gives us instructions.
It would probably be
impossible for me
《恐らく ボク１人で
大蛇丸の相手をするのはムリだ…。
to take on Orochimaru alone...
カブトと協力して
大蛇丸を止めるにしても…。
But even if I can stop Orochimaru
by working together with Kabuto...
he'll find out immediately that
I'm not Sasori by my fighting style...
戦い方で ボクがサソリでないことは
すぐ バレてしまう…。
かといって ３人を呼べば…。
Even so, if I call those three...
then Kabuto will find out
who I am
今度は カブトにこちらの素性がバレて
拘束は厄介になる…。
and it will become difficult
to capture him...
すぐに ３人を呼んで
どちらも倒すか➡
Either I have to immediately call
the three and defeat both of them...
それとも 呼ばずに
このままひくか…。
or retreat as is without calling them...
その どちらかだが…》
I'll have to do one or the other...
《バレたのか… いや 違うな…。
Have I been discovered?
No... that's not it...
これは どういうことだ…!?》
What's the meaning of this?!
潜影多蛇手！
Multiple Striking Shadow Snake!
(大蛇丸)これは…
木遁忍術での変わり身…。
This is a Substitution created
with the Wood Style Ninjutsu...
あなた… まさか…。
You... could it be...?
大蛇丸様。
コイツが サソリの本体ですか？
Orochimaru-sama.
Is this Sasori's real body?
No... It isn't...
いいえ… 違うわ…。
カブト…。
お前 サソリの部下だったくせに➡
Kabuto... you didn't know
his real face
even though you were
his subordinate?
本当の顔も知らないでいたの？
いつも傀儡の中に隠れてる➡
He was a broody guy
who always stayed hidden
inside his puppets, after all...
陰気なヤツでしたからね…。
どういうことだ…？
What's the meaning of this...?!
(ヤマト)カブト…！
お前は暁のスパイのはず…！
Kabuto... you were supposed
to be an Akatsuki spy...
Weren't you caught in one
of Sasori's Jutsu all this time?!
(ヤマト)サソリに ずっと術をかけらて
いたんじゃなかったのか!?
そんな術 とっくに大蛇丸様が
解いてくれた。
Orochimaru-sama... broke that Jutsu
for me ages ago...
(ヤマト)サソリの術に
かかったままのフリをして➡
I can't believe you went
to the other side
pretending to be caught
in one of Sasori's Jutsu...
寝返って いたとはな…！
大蛇丸の術に落ちたか…！
Did you get caught in one
of Orochimaru's Jutsu...?
いや 違うな…。
No... that's not it.
I just empathize with
Orochimaru-sama's ideas.
ボクはただ 大蛇丸様のお考えに
共感しただけさ。
(カブト)ところで アンタは誰だ？
By the way, who are you?
サソリを 始末する予定だったのに
とんだ手違いだよ。
The plan was to take
care of Sasori.
But something has gone
quite wrong.
(大蛇丸)カブト… この子のことは
後で説明してあげるわ。
Kabuto... I'll tell you
about this kid later...
(大蛇丸)それより…
後ろの 子ネズミ３匹も➡
More importantly...
Why don't you call the three
little mice behind you over here?
ここへ 呼んだらどう…？
《すべて
お見通しってわけか…》
So he's seen through
everything, huh...?
《サクラ : 合図…！》
There's the signal!
また キミか…。
You again, huh...?
幾度か見た顔ね…。
九尾の子もいるみたいだし…。
I've seen that face often...
And it looks like
the Nine-Tails kid's here, too...
少し遊んであげましょうかね…。
Maybe I'll play with you guys a little.
(大蛇丸)サスケ君と
どっちが強くなってるか➡
Let's see who's gotten stronger,
you... or Sasuke-kun.
みてあげるわ…！
Reach for it, reach for it, far away.
todoke todoke tooku e
Now I trust these revived tears to you.
ima wo kishikaisei namida azukete
It begins.
hajimare
A long, long story about you
nagai nagai kimi monogatari
"Tears", "tears".
namidatte namidatte
I want to shed them in happy times
ureshii toki ni nagashitai
So what if I want them to float in pretty puddles?
kirei na mizutamari ukabetai no wa nani
The southern sky,
minami no sora ni
It twinkles.
matataiteiru
From all of the stars meeting.
hoshi no kazu hodo no deai kara
Learning about love, receiving a map.
ai wo manandari chizu wo morattari
Are connected.
tsunagatteku
Reach for it, reach for it, far away.
todoke todoke tooku e
(カブト)大蛇丸様は
これまでに三度転生している。
Now I trust these revived tears to you.
ima wo kishikaisei namida azukete
(カブト)第一の転生については 不明。
(カブト)
木ノ葉崩しの際に みせた姿が➡
Someday a new page will turn.
itsuka mekuru peeji ni
２人目の器らしい。
本当は 写輪眼を持つ
うちは イタチの体が➡
I'm sure it'll be filled with lots of people
kitto takusan no hito ga afureru
欲しかったようだけど
入手に 失敗…。
(カブト)弟のサスケ君に狙いを変更し
四人衆と 君麻呂を使って➡
It begins,
hajimare
A long, long story about you.
nagai nagai kimi monogatari
サスケ君を
引き入れようとしたのだが…。
(カブト)三代目との戦いで
両腕を封印されてしまった➡
Next Episode
大蛇丸様の肉体は
想像以上に早く限界を迎えた…。
You're starting to become more like
a Jinchuriki aren't you, Naruto-kun.
(カブト)急を要すると判断したボクは➡
That's...!
What kind of... Chakra is that?!
実験体たちを戦わせ➡
The air stings....
There's no mistake.
The Fox Spirit's Cloak...!
最後まで勝ち残った者を
器に選んだ。
That's the Jinchuriki's power?
それが現在の器 幻幽丸だ。
I can tell just by the feel of it.
This... This horrible Chakra...
あれから すでに３年。
次の器も
順調に育っているようだし➡
It's not a Chakra quality
that can be controlled!
楽しみだね…。
So this is Uzumaki Naruto's...
The Nine-Tail's power...!
これは すべて ボクの独り言。
The Nine-Tails Unleashed!!
(カブト)気にしないでくれ…。
フフフ…。
Next Time: "The Nine-Tails Unleashed"
"SECRET: KABUTO'S MEDICAL FILE"
Orochimaru-sama has been reincarnated
three times so far.
Details about the first reincarnation
are unclear.
It seems the form he appeared
as during the destruction
of the Leaf was the second body.
It seems he actually wanted
the body of Uchiha Itachi
who possesses the Sharingan.
But he failed to get his body.
Orochimaru then set his sights on
Itachi's younger brother Sasuke-kun instead
and attempted to bring him
over to his side
by using the Sound Ninja Four
as well as Kimimaro.
But in the battle with the Third,
both of his arms were sealed...
and his flesh reached its limit much
faster than could've been imagined.
As I judged this to be
a matter of urgency,
I had the test subjects
battle each other...
and selected the last one standing
as the next body.
And that is his current body,
Genyuumaru.
It's already been
three years since then.
It looks like the next body is
steadily approaching completion.
I'm looking forward to it.
All of this is just me thinking aloud.
You don't need to concern
yourself with it.